Guide to the Law School. External Relations records, 1991-2000.
Law School. External relations records, 1991-2000.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Law School. External Relations records, 1991-2000.
18-10-3186.
Cornell Law School. External Relations.
14 audio cassettes and videos.
Audio cassettes, videocassettes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Includes audio cassette tapes and videos of various events at the Cornell Law School.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes audio cassette tapes and videos of various events at the Cornell Law School, including reunions, advisory council meetings and talks, including one by Sol Linowitz.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Law School.; Linowitz, Sol M., 1913-.; Cornell Law School. Advisory Council.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
Class reunions--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Audio cassettes.; Videocassettes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Videocassettes
  - Cornell Law School Today - video #540, Apr. 7, 1993 (Box 1)
  - NYS Supreme Court Appellate Division Third Dept. - Judges - video #541, Apr. 18, 1996 (Box 1)
  - NYS Supreme Court Appellate Division Third Dept. - Attorneys - video #542, Apr. 18, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Steven Roberts - video #543, June 7, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - All Classes Dinner - video #544, June 1999 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Panel Discussion - video #545, June 1999 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Graham - video #546, June 1998 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Panel Discussion - video #547, June 1998 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Marlin Fitzwater - video #548, June 1996 (Box 1)
- Audio Cassettes
  - Law Conference - Minorities - tr #7888, Sept. 1986 (Box 1)
  - Cornell Law School: Past, Present & Future - tr #7889 (Box 1)
  - Dean Osgood's Talks in Boston and Washington, DC - tr #7890, Oct. 1998 (Box 1)
  - Curia Speech - Sol Linowitz '37 - Cornell Club - tr #7891, Nov. 6, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Judge Burton Robert's speech - tr #7892, Jan. 24, 1997 (Box 1)
  - "Let's Get Acquainted" - Al Neimeth - tr #7893 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council meeting - tr #7894, Sept. 15, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council - Business meeting - tr #7895, Sept. 1996 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council - Business meeting - tr #7896, Sept. 1996 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council - Legal Workplace - tr #7897, Sept. 1996 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Panel Discussion - "Civil Justice" - tr #7898, June 7, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Steve Robert's speech - tr #7899, June 7, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Saturday lunch - tr #7900, June 1998 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - Saturday dinner - Graham speaker -tr #7901, June 1998 (Box 1)
  - Reunion Lunch - tr #7903, June 1999 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - lunch - tr #7905, June 2000 (Box 1)
  - Reunion - dinner - tr #7906, June 2000 (Box 1)